Guide to the Daily Worker and the Daily World Negatives Collection PHOTOS.223.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI: Contact Sheets, 1918-2006
  - Subseries A: Contact Sheets with Shoot Numbers
    - Reform Democrats Support Rent Control, Tenants Meeting on Rent Control. 93rd Street, New York, New York. Jerome Kretchmer, Albert Blumenthal, Alex Rosenberg, Benjamin Rosenthal, Ted Weiss., Jun 3, 1967 (Box 31, Shoot 670031)
    - Democrats for Peace at Manhattan Center, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Jun 15, 1967 (Box 31, Shoot 670038)
    - Welfare Workers Protest [at] City Hall., Jun 23, 1967 (Box 31, Shoot 670044)
    - Harlem Youth Unemployment Protest [at] City Hall, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Jun 27, 1967 (Box 31, Shoot 670049)
    - Welfare Recipients Protest at City Hall., Jun 30, 1967 (Box 31, Shoot 670050)
    - Railroad Strike. Photos by Bill Andrews., Jul 17, 1967 (Box 31, Shoot 670071)
    - "Flower Children" at Anti-War Protest Outside Waldorf Astoria Hotel, Where Lyndon B. Johnson Was Speaking. Photos by Bill Andrews., Summer 1967 (Box 31, Shoot 670084)
    - Hiroshima Day Direct Action Project by National Mobilization for Peace at USS Peary, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Aug 6, 1967 (Box 31, Shoot 670090)
    - Farm Workers, Riverhead, Long Island., Aug 1967 (Box 31, Shoot 670099)
    - Rally to Free H. Rap Brown, Federal Court House, Foley Square, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Sep 1967 (Box 31, Shoot 670102)
    - Youth for Jobs Picket Line, City Hall, New York, New York., Sep 1967 (Box 31, Shoot 670118)
    - Pro and Anti-War Tables, Columbia University, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Oct 11, 1967 (Box 31, Shoot 670120)
    - Anti-Draft Protest, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Oct 16, 1967 (Box 31, Shoot 670121)
    - Demonstration Against Dean Rusk, from Hilton Hotel (6th Avenue and 53rd Street) to Times Square, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Nov 1967 (Box 31, Shoot 670135)
    - Dow Chemical Company Protest, City College, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Nov 1967 (Box 31, Shoot 670140)
    - "Art" Shots - Bread and Puppet Mask, Bird on Statue of Eagle, Riverside Drive and 72nd Street, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Nov 1967 (Box 31, Shoot 670143)
    - Whitehall Week Anti-Draft Demonstration, Lutheran Church, Brooklyn, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Dec 4, 1967 (Box 31, Shoot 670147)
    - Whitehall Week Anti-Draft Demonstration, Whitehall Induction Center, New York, New York. Participants include Benjamin Spock. Photos by Bill Andrews., Dec 5, 1967 (Box 31, Shoot 670148)
    - Whitehall Week Anti-Draft Demonstration, Whitehall Induction Center, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Dec 8, 1967 (Box 31, Shoot 670152)
    - Stokely Carmichael at John F. Kennedy Airport, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Dec 11, 1967 (Box 31, Shoot 670154)
    - Painting of Eugene C. Andrews by Bill Andrews., Jan 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680018)
    - Sanitation Workers Strike, City Hall, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Feb 2, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680027)
    - Sanitation Workers Strike, Lower East Side, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Feb 9, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680036)
    - John J. DeLury (President, Sanitationmen's Union) Released from County Jail, 37th Street, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Feb 21, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680044)
    - W. E. B. Du Bois Centennial Meeting, Carnegie Hall, New York, New York. Participants include Martin Luther King, Jr., Aram Khachaturian (composer), J. H. O'Dell (Associate Managing Editor, Freedomways magazine), Ossie Davis, Jesus Colon, James Baldwin, Pete Seeger, Len Chandler, Cynthia McCoy and Lorenz Graham. Photos by Bill Andrews., Feb 23, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680045)
    - John J. DeLury and Jack Bigel at Press Conference, Commodore Hotel, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Feb 23, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680047)
    - Caroline Black., Feb 24, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680048)
    - Sanitation Workers Facilities Press Tour (Garage #1, Canal Street, West Side Drive), New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Feb 24, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680049)
    - Protest Against Potential Use of Nuclear Weapons in Vietnam, United States Mission to the United Nations (45th Street and 1st Avenue), New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Feb 24, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680050)
    - Anti-Nuclear War Rally, United Nations Plaza, New York, New York. Participants include Dagmar Wilson (Women Strike for Peace), Linda Morse, Otto Nathan, Phillip Morrison (Massachusetts Institute of Technology), Daniel Berrigan and Cenie Spears (Alumni, Orangeburg College)., Feb 24, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680051)
    - Protest Against Orangeburg (South Carolina) Massacre, United States Mission to United Nations (45th Street and 1st Avenue), New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Feb 24, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680052)
    - Demonstrations and Arrests at Columbia University Gym Construction Site, Morningside Heights (113th Street), New York, New York. Participants include Kendall Smith and William Stanley. Photos by Bill Andrews., Feb 28, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680055)
    - Demonstration for Muhammad Ali, Madison Square Garden, New York, New York. Participants include Matt Weinstein, Jarvis Tyner, Jose Stevens, Harry Edwards, William Booth (New York Human Rights Commission), Carlos Russell, Charles Kenyatta, Dixie Bayo., Mar 4, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680058)
    - Moratorium Day Protest at Columbia University to Protest Vietnam War and Draft. Participants include John H. E. Friend (Professor of Political Science at CCNY), Bernadine Dohrn. David B. Truman (Vice President and Provost of Columbia) also pictured. Photos by Bill Andrews., Mar 13, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680062)
    - Daily World Meeting, Town Hall, New York, New York. Participants include Carl Winter, John Pittman, Nora North, Tito Nolasco, Ellie Laibman, Gus Hall and Ken Bailey., Mar 14, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680067)
    - Resistance Meeting, Brooklyn College, Brooklyn, New York. Participants include Joan Baez, Fred Rosen, David HarrisIra Sandperl., Mar 20, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680070)
    - Nelson Rockefeller Press Conference, Announcing He Will Not Seek Republican Party Nomination for 1968 Presidential Elections, Hilton Hotel, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Mar 21, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680072)
    - Auto Accident, Caton Street and St. Paul's Place, Brooklyn, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Mar 22, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680074)
    - Joan Baez and David Harris Announce Their Marriage at Press Conference, 70th Street and Park Avenue, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Mar 27, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680078)
    - Eugene McCarthy for President Headquarters, 8th Avenue and 58th Street, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Mar 27, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680079)
    - Lyndon B. Johnson Announces He Will Not Seek Re-election. Photos taken off TV., March 31, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680081)
    - Robert F. Kennedy at Overseas Press Club (40th Street and 5th Avenue), New York, New York. Ethel Kennedy and Ted Sorenson also pictured. Photos by Bill Andrews., Apr 1, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680084)
    - Anti-War and Anti-Draft Demonstration by the Resistance, Boston Common, Boston, Massachusetts., Apr 3, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680086)
    - Draft Card Refusal Rally, Central Park, New York, New York. Participants include David Zimmerman (Resistance), David Miller, Thomas Hayes (Episcopal Peace Fellowship), Mitchell Goodman, Joan Baez and David Harris. Photos by Bill Andrews., Apr 3, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680087)
    - Police Arrest African American Youths for Window Breaking and Disorderly Conduct in Times Square on Night of Martin Luther King's Death. Photos by Bill Andrews., Apr 4, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680088)
    - Youth Memorial Rally for Martin Luther King, Jr., Central Park, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Apr 5, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680090)
    - Memorial March for Martin Luther King, Jr. from Central Park to City Hall, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Apr 5, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680091)
    - Du Bois Club Picket Line Protesting Murder of Martin Luther King, Jr., Times Square, New York, New York., Apr 5, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680092)
    - Religious Service Memorial for Martin Luther King, Jr., Central Park, New York, New York. Participants include Terrence Cooke, Nelson A. Rockefeller, John V. Lindsay, Percy Sutton, Wyatt T. Walker, Theodore Weiss, Paul O'Dwyer, Charles Kenyatta and Sammy Davis, Jr., Apr 7, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680093)
    - James Forman (SNCC) at Memorial for Martin Luther King, Jr., Central Park, New York, New York. Accuses Nelson A. Rockfeller of signing "Shoot to Kill" Bill and not helping H. Rap Brown., Apr 7, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680094)
    - Harlem Memorial March for Martin Luther King, Jr., Down 7th Avenue from 145th Street to Central Park Mall, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Apr 7, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680095)
    - African American Youth Protest Murder of Martin Luther King, Jr., Near United Nations, New York, New York., Apr 8, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680097)
    - Young People Give Away "Our King Will Never Die" Armbands Near United Nations, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Apr 8, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680098)
    - Memorial to Martin Luther King by New York University Interfaith Council, Washington Square Park, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Apr 10, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680099)
    - Demonstration for Public Housing, Housing and Urban Development Department (357 Broadway), New York, New York. Participants include Jane Benedict (Metropolitan Council on Housing) and Major Owens. Photos by Bill Andrews., Apr 10, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680100)
    - Memorial for Martin Luther King, Jr., Union Square, New York, New York. Participants include Thomas J. Mackell (District Attorney, Queens), James Farmer (CORE), and members of Teamsters Local 237. Photos by Bill Andrews., Apr 11, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680102)
    - Athletes Protest Racism and Fascism in South Africa, 777 UN Plaza, New York, New York. From left to right in photos 5 to 9: Heywood Dotson, Kwaku Ohene-Phrempong, George Houser, Steve Mokone, Ruben Amarlo, Jim Bouton., Apr 11, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680103)
    - Yippies in Central Park, New York, New York. Bill Andrews, Marcia Gutman, Fred Kirkpatrick pictured., Apr 14, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680106)
    - Food for Poor People's Campaign in Washington, D.C., Central Park, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Apr 14, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680107)
    - War Tax Protest by War Resisters League, Internal Revenue Service (120 Church Street), New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Apr 15, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680110)
    - Protest Against Greek Military Dictatorship, Greek Embassy (79th Street between Madison and Park Avenues), New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Apr 21, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680117)
    - Brooklyn Black Community Leaders (CORE) Stage Sit-in at Long Island University (Flatbush and Dekalb Avenues, Brooklyn, New York) and Hold Provost Hostage., Apr 25, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680123)
    - Communications Workers of America (CWA) Rally, Murray Street near City Hall, New York, New York. Participants include Harry Van Arsdale. Photos by Bill Andrews., Apr 25, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680124)
    - Columbia Students Rally, 116th and Amsterdam Avenue, New York, New York., Apr 26, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680125)
    - Peace Parade Down Central Park West to 72nd Street, New York, New York. Participants include Pete Seeger, David Livingston (District 65), Coretta Scott King, Jim Haughton (Harlem Unemployment Council), William Sloane Coffin, and African American veterans. Photos by Bill Andrews., Apr 27, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680128)
    - Pro-War Parade, Up 5th Avenue from 36th Street to 44th Street. Photos by Bill Andrews., Apr 27, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680129)
    - Columbia Students Take Over Buildings (Math Building, Low Library, Avery Hall, Hamilton Hall). Right-wing students attempt to prevent food from reaching students in Low Library. Aides to John Lindsay Barry Goetter and Sid Davidow pictured., April 29, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680132)
    - Columbia University Students Rally to Protest Police Brutality and Arrests. Participants include Mark Rudd. Photos by Mark Brody., Apr 30, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680133)
    - May Day Demonstration, Union Square, New York, New York. Participants include Esther Carroll (garment worker), Henry Winston, Claude Lightfoot, Jarvis Tyner, Chaim Suller (Morning Freiheit), Rasheed Storey, Joseph North, Grace Mora Newman, Florynce Kennedy (attorney), Gus Hall, Barbara Dane, Tom Cornell (Catholic Worker) and Ken Cloke (National Lawyers Guild)., May 1, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680138)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Memorial Parade, Park Slope, Brooklyn, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., May 5, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680139)
    - Parents, Teachers and Children Protest Cuts in Education Funds, Kings Highway Democratic Club, 15th Street and Kings Highway, Brooklyn, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., May 9, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680140)
    - Poor People's March, from Armory at 142nd Street and East River, across 142nd Street, down 7th Avenue, across 116th Street, down 3rd Avenue, across 101st Street, down 5th Avenue to Central Park Mall, New York, New York. Participants include Ralph Abernathy, James Orange, George A. Francis (Passamaquoddy People, Maine) and Beulah Sanders (Citywide Welfare Rights Committee). Photos by Bill Andrews., May 11, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680142)
    - Brownsville Junior High School 271. Rhody McCoy (chairman of local governing board) pictured., May 15, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680143)
    - Sit-in by Columbia University Students and Harlem Residents Protesting Columbia University's Slumlord Practices. 618 West 114th Street, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., May 18, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680147)
    - Poor People's Campaign, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania and Washington, D.C. (Resurrection City). Photos by Nora North., May 18, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680149)
    - Eugene McCarthy Rally, Madison Square Garden, New York, New York. Participants include Phil Ochs, Dustin Hoffman, Lillian Hellman, Tony Randall Arthur Miller, Roscoe Lee Browne, Paul O'Dwyer, Jose Ferrer, Alan Arkin, Dick Van Dyke, Tedd Weiss, Lillian Heyman, Robert Lowell, Allaird Lowenstein, Clarence B. Jones, Cornelius Givens, James H. Scheuer, James Shenton (Columbia University professor), Howard Moody, Renee Taylor (actress), Gary Moore. Photos by Bill Andrews., May 19, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680151)
    - Columbia University After a Night of Violence and Bloodshed., May 22, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680154)
    - Yonkers People for Peace Demonstration for Cease-Fire in Vietnam. 98 8th Avenue and 38th Street at Madison Avenue, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., May 25, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680156)
    - Puerto Rican Poor People's Campaign Rally, Central Park, New York, New York. Participants include Vieques Steel Band, Pepe y Flora, Frank Espada, Gilberto Valentin (New York Human Rights Commission), Jacob K. Javits and Joe Monserrat (Department of Labor, Puerto Rico)., May 26, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680157)
    - Eugene McCarthy, Robert F. Kennedy Debate (Los Angeles, California), Photos Taken from ABC-TV Channel 7, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Jun 1, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680162)
    - Anti-Imperialist Coalition Picket French Consulate (74th Street and 5th Avenue, New York, New York) in Support of French Workers and Students.Photos by Bill Andrews., Jun 1, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680163)
    - Herman Ferguson, with Arthur Harris, Lydia Williams and Gula Glover at Queens County Criminal Court, New York., Jun 3, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680164)
    - Columbia University "Counter-Commencement" March and Demonstration, Morningside Heights, New York, New York. Participants include Dwight McDonald, Alexander Erlich (Columbia University Professor of Economics), Erich Fromm and Harold Taylor (former President of Sarah Lawrence College). Photos by Bill Andrews., 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680165)
    - Columbia University Students and Well-wishers Support Columbia University Graduates Who Walk Out of Commencement, 116th Street and Amsterdam Avenue, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Jun 4, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680166)
    - Welfare Department Clients Line Up Outside Welfare Centers, Melrose and 161st Streets; Grand Concourse and 175th Street, Bronx, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Jun 5, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680168)
    - Eugene McCarthy Speaking at Fellowship of Reconciliation Dinner, Hotel Commodore (42nd Street and Lenox Avenue), New York, New York. Robert Lowell, Ruth Gage Colby, Paul O'Dwyer and Albert Haesller also Pictured., Jun 13, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680169)
    - Prospect Park, Brooklyn, New York. Baseball games and statue of Abraham Lincoln. Photos by Bill Andrews., Jun 16, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680172)
    - Poor People's Campaign Solidarity Day, Washington, District of Columbia. Participants include Hubert Humphrey, Eugene McCarthy, Ossie Davis, Herman Badillo, Walter Reuther, Pete Seeger, Jerry Butler, Peter, Paul and Mary, Clara Ward, Bill Cosby, Noble Sissle, Mary Beth McCarthy, William F. Ryan, Jacob Javits, Eartha Kitt, Coretta Scott King, Everett Parker, Mad Bear, Roy Wilkins, Whitney Young, Charles Percy, Dorothy Height, Roberta Parks, Don Leace, Johnnie Tillmon, Peggy Terry, James Bevel, Cleveland Robinson, Gilberto Gerena Valentin and the Flying Nesbitts., Jun 19, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680176)
    - Coney Island and Brighton Beach, Brooklyn, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Jun 29, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680178)
    - Ted Bassett., Jun 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680179)
    - Joe Brandt., Jun 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680180)
    - Erik Bert., Jun 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680181)
    - Ken Bailey., Jun 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680182)
    - Carla Andrews, aka Caroline Ballin., Jun 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680183)
    - Mark Brody., Jun 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680184)
    - Carl Bloice., Jun 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680185)
    - Carl Winter., Jun 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680186)
    - Dick Greenleaf., Jun 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680187)
    - Tim Wheeler., Jun 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680188)
    - Ben Levine., Jun 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680190)
    - Doris May., Jun 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680189)
    - Jim Peake., Jun 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680191)
    - Dorothy Thompson., Jun 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680192)
    - Mike Kaufman., Jun 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680193)
    - Seymour Joseph., Jun 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680194)
    - Mike Davidow., Jun 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680195)
    - Sarah Paul., Jun 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680196)
    - Joseph North., Jun 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680197)
    - Dave Carpenter., Jun 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680198)
    - Simon Gerson., Jun 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680199)
    - Phil Bonosky., Jun 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680200)
    - John Pittman., Jun 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680201)
    - Juan "Tito" Nolasco., Jun 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680202)
    - Calypso Band, Central Park, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Jul 7, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680205)
    - Communist Party of the United States of America Convention, Hotel Diplomat, New York, New York. Participants include Claude Lightfoot (frames 7-8), Henry Winston (frames 11-12), John Pittman (frame 13), Gus Hall (frames 22-26), Charlene Mitchell (frames 31-40), William L. Patterson (frames 40-42), Mike Zagarell., Jul 7, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680206)
    - Patterson, New Jersey. Southern Christian Leadership Conference (SCLC) Offices, Johnny's Barbershop, Catholic Community Center, City Hall, Lawrence Kramer, Jr. (mayor) pictured. Photos by Bill Andrews., Jul 9, 1968 - Jul 10, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680207)
    - African American and Puerto Rican Youth Demonstrate for Jobs, City Hall, New York, New York. Participants include Willie J. Smith (Director, New York City Neighborhood Youth Corps)., Jul 10, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680208)
    - Trash in Streets, Brooklyn, New York. McKillen, Seigel, Moore Streets and Manhattan Avenue., Jul 11, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680209)
    - Demonstration to Free Huey Newton, Offices of State of California (1188 6th Avenue), New York, New York. Participants include members of Du Bois Clubs, Peace and Freedom Party and Black Panthers., Jul 15, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680211)
    - Columbia University Students Picket Criminal Courts, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Jul 16, 1968 - Jul 17, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680212)
    - Anti-War and Anti-Humphrey Demonstration, Hammarskjold Square (47th Street and 1st Avenue), New York, New York. Participants include Stanley Taxel, Dave McReynolds, Bern Harrison (Vietnam Veterans for McCarthy), Jack Bronstein (New York State Senator) and Richard Reilly., Jul 20, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680215a)
    - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade Outing, Camp Wingdale, Monroe, New York. Arlo Guthrie also pictured. Photos by Bill Andrews., Jul 21, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680217)
    - Kids Release Water from Fire Hydrant and Cops Try to Close It, 25th Street between 9th and 10th Avenues, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Jul 22, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680220)
    - Pickets at Metropolitan Life Insurance Company, Madison Avenue and 24th Street, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Jul 23, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680221)
    - Poverty in Coney Island, Brooklyn, New York. Rickey Kay (frames 44-4), Willie Kay (frames 5-6), Endell Kay (frames 8-9) and Nicholas Stevenson Sr. (frames 15-16) pictured., Jul 25, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680222)
    - Bombing of Grove Press, 80 University Place, New York, New York., Jul 26, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680224)
    - Alcoholic Man at Carnegie Hall (7th Avenue and 57th Street), New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Aug 3, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680227)
    - Bombing of Bank of Tokyo Trust Company, 49th Street near Park Avenue, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Aug 3, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680228)
    - Michael Locilento (AWOL pacifist) Takes Refuge in Washington Square Methodist Church (4th Street near 6th Avenue), New York, New York. Doris and Daniel Locilento (parents) and Richard Neuhaus also pictured., Aug 3, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680229)
    - Peace Rally, Times Square, New York, New York with March to United States Army Armory at 34th Street and Park Avenue. Participants include Charlene Mitchell, Mary Kochiyama, Dalton James (Vietnam veteran), Hubert James (Citywide Welfare Committee), Lenny Brody, Herman Ferguson, Thomas Lee Hayes (Episcopal Peace Fellowship), Bern Harrison (Vietnam Vets for McCarthy), and Barbara Dane. Photos by Bill Andrews., Aug 3, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680231)
    - John Gallo., Aug 5, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680232)
    - Bombing of Communist Party of the United States of America Headquarters, 23 West 26th Street, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Aug 6, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680233)
    - New York City Skyline Views from Rockefeller Center Rooftop. Photos by Bill Andrews., Aug 12, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680236)
    - George Chaiken and Richie Bell (draft refusers) at Fort Hamilton Induction Center, Brooklyn, New York. Grace Mora Newman, Carolyn Rivers, Jose Ristorucci and Louis Salzberg (FBI informant, with camera) also pictured., Aug 13, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680237)
    - Registered Nurses Picket for Higher Salaries at City Hall, New York, New York., Aug 13, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680238)
    - Rally for Eugene McCarthy, Madison Square Garden, New York, New York. Participants include Herman Badillo, Joseph Rauh, David Livingston, Harold Willens, Ed Koch, Eugene Nickerson, Harry Belafonte, Leonard Bernstein, Richie Havens, Carl Reiner, Paul O'Dwyer, John Kenneth Galbraith and Richard Chavez. Photos by Bill Andrews., Aug 15, 1968 (Box 31, Shoot 680240)